CARMEN NAVARRO TIMÓN

I am a designer who knows how to code and loves it.

I qualified as a Higher Technician in Multiplatform Application Development in December 2020. I have been trained as a fullstack and I am specialised in frontend. I come from the world of design applied to the cultural and artistic sector. I have worked as a freelancer and also in large teams in museums, theatres, TV and cinema. In order to direct towards the digital sector everything I have learnt during these years of experience in design, I have taken several professional courses in Product Design, Interaction Design and UX/UI Design.

I am passionate about the technological universe for its enormous potential both in its capacity to increase people's cognitive abilities and its power to generate new experiences, transmit new sensations and emotions.





carmen.navarro.timon@gmail.com



+ 34 - 647627463



Navalafuente. Madrid. Spain.

PORTFOLIO: www.armatedearte.es https://github.com/CarmelitaDescalza/portfolio



EXPERIENCE

2020-2022. Fullstack Developer. Product Designer UX/UI. Freelance. Alalpha Tech. https://www.alalpha.es.

2020-2022. Product Designer UX. AR/VR. ARAN Art Network. https://aran.live

09/2020-12/2020. Frontend Wordpress and Product Designer, UX/UI. Internship at Dreamsign, digital marketing.

2019 - 2020. Backend developer. Product Designer, UX/UI. Project "BeRoutes", tourist routes APP.

07/2008 - 11/2019. Design, production and management of artistic and cultural products and projects. Freelance. https://www.descalza.es



EDUCATION

2018 – 2020 Higher Technician in Multiplatform Application Development (C.E.V.) HND (Higher National Diploma)

2008 – 2009 Diploma in Costume Design for Cinema. (E.C.A.M.)

2002 – 2008 Degree in Art History. (U.A.M.) Universidad Autónoma de Madrid.

1999 – 2002 1°, 2° y 3° year of Industrial Design. . (I.E.D) Istituto Europeo di Design.

CERTIFICATES

2022 UX UI Professional Course. Asociación Española Programadores Informaticos.

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures. Certification 300h. FreeCodeCamp. 2022

SKILLS

Frontend

HTML **CSS JavaScript TypeScript** Angular React SVG **GSAP**

Backend

WebGL

Java Spring SQL **AWS**

AR-VR

C# Unity Vuforia

Design 3D/2D

3DStudio **Autocad** Photoshop Ilustrator

Design UX/UI

Draw.io AdobeXD Figma

Agile

Kanban Scrum Lean Trello Git

Languages

Ingles B1 -B2 Frances A1 Italiano A1 Mod. Greek A2

Others

Honesty **Empathy** Good ideas Resolute Humour **Quick learner**

> I like do things well